a!
あ!
what?
何?
Is it important?
大切だい?
I'm so excited, something is coming out.
興奮してさ なんか出ちゃってんだよね
why?
なん で?
There's water over there.
そちらなんか水だよ
Since I put out so much, I have to concentrate it.
あ んまいっぱい出したから、濃縮しないと
It came out and I was so excited that it was a mess.
出 てきた 興奮してるから、ぐちゃぐちゃ あ、
It's true.
本当だ
You set it up there.
立てたね そこの
So what should I do?
どう しようかな そこでそんな、
Does it come out like that?
そういう感じで出るの?
Then I tried saying
そしたら言ってみた
healthy type
ヘ ルシーなタイプ
There's only one
1つ しかない
Will I do it again?
や っぱりしちゃう?
My legs are really tight. Is it difficult?
足やっぱりめっちゃしてる 難しい?
difficult
難しい
Your legs are long
足 長いね
It's amazing, it won't stop, it's so wet, what's this?
すごい ね、止まんないね びちゃびちゃじゃん なにこれ、
What's going on?
なんとなってんの?
foot on foot
足に足ついて
What's going on?
なん となってんの?
copper?
どう?
I feel terrible.
やばい気がするね
No Power has been injected
無 パワーに注入完了
One word of impression: It felt good, thank you very much.
感 想一言 気持ちよかったです ありがとうございました